I love thee with the breath,
smiles, tears, of all my life.
And if God choose, I shall love thee better after death.
'Cause this is outcast country and I'm feeling
right at home.
'Cause this is out cast country and I'm feeling
Yeah, I ain't never going back, never gonna
be alone.
Control, this is Bird One. Suspect is continuing on I-70 southbound.
Road ahead is clear.
Copy, Bird one. Highway units maintain distance.
Oh,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, yeah.
Control, suspect is coming in hot.
Roadblock, report status, over.
Copy. Traffic detoured. Roadblock in position and ready to lay
strips.
Oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh.
Oh.
Yeah,
out
cast country and I'm
feeling right at home.
'Cause this is out cast country
and I'm feeling right at home.
Guess we should've blocked the on-ramp, eh, Sarge?
Oh.
Hello?
This is Major James Tilton, Commanding, Arkansas State Police Highway Patrol
Division.
How do you do, Major?
Been better. Thanks for asking. Am I speaking to a Ryan Flanagan?
Fang.
Did you say Fang?
Roger that.
Well, Fang, you are driving a stolen vehicle far in excess of my beloved state's
posted speed limit.
Firm grasp at the glaringly obvious.
You're senior command, all right.
Well, after fleeing a crime scene in Kentucky, I've been told that you've been
quite busy. You wanna tell me what happened?
Did you call to list everything I already know, Major?
Because that'll get old real quick.
Well, my hope is to resolve this situation peaceably before anybody gets hurt.
Is there anybody that you'd like to speak with to help us fix this?
You got a wife, right? Down in Kentucky?
Ex-wife.
Tara?
I was a Marine with second LAR in Sangin.
Then in the interest of full disclosure, you should know that I
consider all jarheads to be knuckle-dragging cave
dwellers.
I don't necessarily disagree. What branch were you, Fang?
This conversation has reached its expiration date.
Besides,
guys like us don't get justice. We get forgotten.
Please, please, don't hang up. I'm really scared that bad things are gonna happen
if we don't figure this out.
Bad things always happen, Major,
regardless of how much the s*******s in charge think they have figured out.
Another beautiful day in paradise, hey, boys?
Keep it away from the civilians.
Put in their hands thy bruising irons of wrath.
Captain, would you stop Wiz from quoting Shakespeare?
He makes the rest of us feel illiterate.
I'll never dampen a young man's intellectual fire, Tank.
Well, then, I should be able to hold Hustler's Forum.
You do you, big fella.
Bridget touched Carl's erogenous zone with a bionic tongue.
Hey, Captain, then I should be allowed to sing "The Man in Black."
I'm officially a kindergarten teacher.
There is a house in
New Orleans. They
call the Rising Sun.
Where
many
a poor boy
to destruction
have gone.
Hey, guys, that's not in the brochure.
Can we do an orbit?
Roger that.
They're talking about us.
RPG right.
RPG down. Move fast, kick a*s.
Move fast, kick a*s.
RPG right.
Mayday.
Mayday. Mayday. Whiskey two-six
going down.
No comms. Brace. Brace. Brace.
How may I help you, Todd?
Todd's gone.
How would you like to be addressed?
Fang.
How may I help you, Fang?
Is this like Siri?
I'm Helene, digital automative concierge, designed
to make driving more comfortable.
Handy.
Let's see. Helene,
find me a falafel restaurant in
Denmark.
One moment while I look that up.
You were right. First Special Forces,
Fort Campbell,
three tours.
Bronze Star and Purple Heart.
The Persian Prince in Copenhagen is the top reviewed on
Yelp. Gina S. from Hamburg gives the Persian Prince four
stars. Quote, "I closed my eyes and thought I woke up in
Amman," unquote.
Did you translate that review from Danish?
German.
His nickname is Fang. Special Ops guys all use these nicknames.
Thanks.
And he ran Jungle Warfare School for two years.
I heard guys had to kill a crocodile with their bare hands to graduate that school.
Major,
the FBI is here.
Of course they are.
What is the length of the Trans-Siberian Railroad?
5,478 miles, Fang.
How about the most effective way to train a house cat to use
the toilet?
One moment while I look that up.
When you find it, could you email the link to my ex-wife?
Certainly, Fang. What is your ex-wife's email address?
Why does a marriage fail
when both people love each other deeply?
Stop. Stop saying that. You're not happy,
and neither am I.
I know I've had some regression, but I'm better.
You never sleep. You're popping Xanax and Valium like it's candy,
and you're angry. You're still so angry, and then you stopped going to
therapy. You tell them you need a little break. That's not how it works.
Brian, I love you with all my heart, with all my
soul, but I can't
fix you, and I'm completely worn out from trying.
I don't know who I am anymore.
I want a divorce.
Baby.
Hey.
Special Agent Bridge. Special Agent Heller.
Thank y'all for coming down, but I think we got it covered now. Understood, Major.
We're the homicide investigation. Whoa, whoa. Homicide?
Kentucky never gave us any details of that- And we suspect that he's armed with the
murder weapon.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Fang, but I need to inform you that you are
running on the vehicle's reserve fuel supply.
Oh, come on. Screw you, Todd.
I'm unable to address this request.
No, not... How long before I'm out of fuel?
At your current speed, reserve fuel will be exhausted in 3.4
minutes.
How far is the closest airport?
Memorial Field in Hot Springs is 4.6 miles
northwest of your current location.
Can I make it on reserve fuel?
At a much-reduced speed. Would you like me to book you a plane ticket out
of Hot Springs?
Major, suspect has exited the interstate.
Control, this is Bird One. We are terminating aerial pursuit.
Suspect heading west to Hot Springs.
What the hell? Protected airspace for Memorial Field.
Smart man. What, he's trying to fly out?
Get Hot Springs PD on the car, and alert TSA. Already taken care of.
Proceed west on Crane Avenue for three and a half miles,
then turn left on Wells Avenue.
Your destination will be on the right.
At this speed, will we make it?
Yes.
No routing.
Recalculating route.
Control, this is Unit 37. I am in pursuit of suspect
traveling west on Crane Avenue.
All available units, 10-80 in progress.
Try again, Marlene.
Recalculating.
Control, this is unit 44. Have joined pursuit of suspect now heading west
on Wells Avenue.
Control, suspect entered first junkyard on Wells Avenue.
I am unable to identify your current location.
Don't beat yourself up.
Unit 44 splitting off. Moving to the rear of the yard for intercept.
Reserve fuel at 9%.
Suspect's headed north towards rear entrance.
Fuel reserve critical.
Control, 37. Junkyard is clear. Heading to rear entrance.
37, suspect has exited junkyard. Continuing pursuit north and
south on Fairview.
Get more black and whites there now.
And get that car's cell phone tracked.
This report doesn't track with his history. Mm-hmm.
It's not exactly painting a clear picture. Clear as mud.
We've got to hear his side. He doesn't give himself up, his side won't
matter.
You're a bomb, Marlene.
The vehicle's reserve supply has been exhausted.
Son of a...
We got this.
We
got this.
Let's go. Come on. Go! Move it there.
Let's
go.
Keep it
together,
Wiz. Wiz. Wiz.
Keep it together, Wiz.
You got this. You got this, Wiz. We're here.
Hey.
Hey, good morning.
How you doing?
Good.
Ain't she a peach?
Ain't she just? Fill her up, please.
Yes, sir.
Bet that'll get you there quick.
You can say that again.
How long you had her?
Since this morning.
She set you back a pretty penny?
Surprisingly reasonable.
Keep the change.
Thanks.
Hey, I'm
going to let you finish up yourself.
Good choice.
I think that Eric's isn't ever there. He is always there.
I told you, Wiz for Eric. He's there.
You mean Big Head Eric?
Yes.
Yeah, he's never there.
Thank you.
Well, thank you.
You're welcome. Is your friend still coming?
He's already here.
To Wiz,
on the anniversary of his death.
To Wiz.
Wiz. Wiz.
Yeah, she's, uh...
Look at his eyes.
Look at his wrists.
Stay with me. Die before you let...
Stay with me. We got you.
Stay with it.
Yeah, attaboy.
Attaboy. Yeah. Come on, Wiz.
Delphine filed for divorce.
Again?
Yeah, I believe that's a unit record for busted marriages, right?
Three.
Two and one?
I thought she said she talked to the counselor, and she was locked in.
Well, apparently, her position has evolved.
Snake eaters make lethal killers, s**t husbands.
To all wives whose marriage vows
amount to less than a teaspoon of bobcat
p**s.
Tara's engaged.
Says she's too old to be alone.
Who's the f****r?
Some rich Louisville p***k, Todd something or other.
I never met a Todd I didn't want to punch in the throat.
Yeah.
To all rich Louisville p****s with the name of
Todd something or other, who we'd like to punch in the throat.
You ever just want to go out in a blaze of glory?
Every day.
Move fast and kick a*s.
Pardon me, gentlemen.
I believe in miracles
What happened?
Hey,
just promise me you're not going to get into it with him.
Who?
Todd.
He did this to you?
Has he hit you before?
Never.
Did you call the police?
Half the force is f*****g golf buddies.
So listen to me. Just let it go. I called you.
I wanted you to hear it from me first. I already broke it off with him.
He's dead to me, and that's done. Okay?
I promise, I won't hurt him.
That's my sister.
Hey, hon.
Well, the doctor says I'm going to be okay.
Overnight, though.
Yeah, but I want you to get my s**t out of his place.
Can you go there in the morning? He'll be at work all day. No, but...
Oh, right. Okay.
No,
I'm sure. It can wait. I guess it can wait. Thanks.
Hey, I can do it.
Mm-mm.
What? I'll head over first thing, in and out.
He won't even be there. Right?
Right?
Ah.
All right.
Just because he loves you.
Come on.
Come on, dude. Trust me, you want this.
Oh, for God's sake.
Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Wait.
Ryan?
What are you doing here?
Getting Tara's stuff.
Okay.
Tara's not going anywhere, pal. You consider yourself lucky you're not locked
up, or worse. What's worse is breaking and entering.
I'm just standing my ground.
Yeah. Hey. Yeah, I know what you are, what you're capable
of. Todd,
put the gun down. I just need to get Tara's stuff and leave. Stop moving.
On your knees, now.
Goddammit, hands behind your head.
Hey, I called the police when I saw your shitbox in my driveway.
They're on their way. Put the gun down and I'll- I said on your f*****g-
Where is
she? Where is
she?
Aline, honey, I need directions into Texas using
only surface streets.
Certainly, sir.
Check out time, boys.
Grab some gear.
I got you, pal.
It's not late.
Sir,
we've regained air pursuit.
What about ground?
En route.
Should we alert Texas Highway Patrol?
Unfortunately, yes.
You really think you got it all. Until you see me.
I walk in the room, everybody heads down. All eyes on me.
Dad? Dad?
Hey, honey.
You need to come see the TV.
According to police, this chase began in Kentucky.
KJHX 2 Texas has learned that the driver of the stolen red
Shelby is Ryan Flanagan, former Army Special Forces
officer-
Ryan
... who served three combat tours in Afghanistan and has no previous
criminal record.
Apparently, Flanagan fled the crime scene in Kentucky, which we are still trying to
get information on. KJHX 2 Texas-
Hey, tanker.
Captain needs us.
How you been, Walter?
I can't complain, Jim.
Seems that I've been once again called upon to clean up your mess.
So it doesn't end like the last one.
The last one ended in our apprehension of the suspect.
That's one word for it. Yeah, I'm surprised you and your posse didn't just lynch
him in the town square.
Once a suspect crosses that line,
it'll end the way we see fit.
We? You mean you.
Have you even read his bio, Walter?
The crime scene report?
Flanagan was a highly decorated vet.
How do we know this wasn't self-defense?
Well,
I ain't no college boy like you, Jimbo.
But in my experience, person who's innocent, they don't
run.
Certainly not at 100 miles per hour.
May we share your video feed, please?
Why, certainly.
Now why don't you all sit back, relax,
and enjoy the show.
Texas.
Where'd you get this?
Does it matter?
So this bird is stolen.
Hey, I prefer to characterize the status of this aircraft
as borrowed.
You would characterize it as borrowed.
What would they characterize it as?
How many miles to the state line, Helene?
7.1, Fang.
Unidentified caller.
Hello?
Am I speaking to Captain Flanagan?
Who's this?
Laura Coates, producer, Sara Anders, CNN.
May she speak with you live on the air?
Wow. Go ahead, Sara.
I am live with Captain Ryan Flanagan, former US Army Special
Forces.
I was a captain once, Laura, but at the moment, I'm just an old fart who
dreams of racial harmony, religious accord, and
bargain donuts.
We are speaking as you continue to evade police in a high-speed
chase.
If I'd only just returned those library books.
You want to tell us about what happened back in Kentucky, Captain?
Not in the least.
Were you acting in self-defense?
Aren't we all? From an evolutionary standpoint, I mean.
Would you like to tell us why you're fleeing from the police?
Because they're chasing me.
Have you considered surrendering?
I thought I did for a second, but then I realized I just had
to pee.
Captain Flanagan,
is there anything you'd like to say to anyone that might be watching?
Anyone you'd like to talk to?
Yeah.
A guy called Wiz.
I'm sorry I couldn't save you. Wish it had been me
instead of you, kiddo.
The destination is 200 yards ahead.
Who's in the car with you, Captain?
You can go
wherever you want.
And if you mind, we'll take you
there.
Bring me along as your ambience
fair.
And don't lose heart,
my brother.
The rumble road you
walk.
Like a bird traveling
light.
From high above for a better
sight.
They're coming for us. We got you.
We're going home, Wiz.
My brother.
We're going home.
We're going home. Come on.
Come on, Wiz.
We're going home.
I wish you'd sing your song.
When days of gray
stay too long.
Overwatch, do you have eyes on? Control, Overwatch. No shot.
Arkansas HP in line of fire. Have Arkansas HP
pull back.
No.
Gun!
Control, Overwatch. Suspect has retrieved a pistol.
I repeat, suspect is armed. SWAT element is moving.
Hold SWAT where they are.
We're receiving fragmented reports from the Texas Highway Patrol who
are forming the roadblock. That Captain Flanagan is
armed. As you can see from our footage, the vehicle is stopped in
front of the Texas roadblock with Arkansas State Police blocking
its escape from behind. And again, according to the police on the
ground, the driver, Ryan Flanagan,
is now holding a gun.
I
believe
in
miracles.
This is who I am.
Hello, former spouse.
Did you email me a
cat toilet training link?
Technically, my stolen car did.
Hey, I'm going to need you to come home and help me with that.
Can't. Sorry.
You alone?
Howdy, boys.
Why don't you clear out, give me a moment alone with my ex, please?
Yeah. Let's go.
Okay, they're gone.
Ryan,
listen to me.
You've got to give yourself up right now.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can. You've got to.
It's stop s******g around time.
I will never be captured again.
What happened to Wiz
was not your fault.
I couldn't save him.
Yeah, nobody could've, baby.
I was his commander. He was my responsibility. I'm to blame.
Are you hearing me?
It's not yours to carry.
So,
what do you do now?
Oh, escape. Evade. The usual.
But you can't keep running unless you've got someplace to
go.
Oh, I got a place to go.
Okay.
Maybe then you drive. You drive. Drive as fast
as you can.
Go, go,
go,
go, go!
Block all access points.
Locomotion. Locomotion.
Locomotion.
You can't grow no.
Alene,
I need you to find me a road out of here. This beauty ain't built for off-road.
Recalculating route.
There's a station there. It's calling my name.
All God's sinners on that westbound train.
The drunkard's stuck on lifting that three-ton ocean.
The midnight special keeps calling us home, and
that judgment's hot on my trail. Locomotion.
Locomotion. Locomotion.
You can't grow
no. Locomotion. Locomotion. Locomotion. You can't grow no.
Where are you going, Major?
We are going to Texas.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
I'm certain it's not.
I am unable to identify your current location.
I had a feeling you'd say that.
All God's sinners touch that star. Come on, stranger.
Go tell mama. She's been waiting all night long.
Alene, looks like our epic journey together has come to an end.
I'm sorry to hear that, Fang.
This is
going
to hurt.
Our journey continues, Alene.
I'm delighted to hear that, Fang.
Any unit, report status.
We are now into the fifth hour of this chase and roughly 30
miles into northeastern Texas. CNN has learned that
the driver, former US Army Captain Ryan Flanagan,
was a decorated Green Beret wounded multiple times during
combat operations-
He'll never turn himself in
Sounded like you two still have a connection.
Why'd you divorce him?
Let me see. Thinking back upon it,
hmm, none of your f*****g business.
Look, we need all the help we can, and time is not on our side.
Yeah, you mean on his side.
Or whether self-defense was involved.
The FBI continues to issue brief general statements that they
are closely monitoring the situation-
Okay, when he came back that last time,
things were really good for a while.
We were older, things felt more clear.
But something happened when he was over there.
He was captured,
and he was broken.
Do you understand what he sacrificed?
Hey.
What's between us is between us.
The Pentagon has confirmed that Captain Ryan Flanagan,
a Bronze Star recipient and multiple Purple Heart honoree,
was honorably discharged in 2005, having
served with distinction. Wiz's real name was
Wade Melvy. He was a master sergeant in Captain
Flanagan's Special Forces unit. In their final tour in
Afghanistan, their helicopter was shot down and the unit was
captured. During their escape,
Melvy was killed.
Captain Flanagan and the surviving members of the unit served as
pallbearers at Sergeant Melvy's funeral.
The saying, "Never leave a man behind," is a
deeply ingrained principle in the military, especially
within Special Forces.
This sentiment
is a powerful cultural force within the armed services and
fosters a strong sense of responsibility
It appears that application is still standing, even
in this complex scenario.
Does Arkansas already miss me, Major Tilton?
Well, this is Major Walter Pope, Commander of Texas Highway
Patrol.
I stand corrected. Thanks for the welcome mat back there, Major.
Well, now, Captain Flanagan,
y'all better stop this nonsense or things are going to get a whole lot worse for
you.
Sounds like a threat.
And I tend to respond aggressively to those.
In my state,
when a suspect resists arrest in a vehicle,
law enforcement's within their rights to open fire on that vehicle.
Texas, where the entire state sports a collective hard-on every
time a gun is fired.
Well,
as I'm sure you know from combat,
whenever rifle fire is involved,
stray bullets are always a possibility.
Listen to me, you inbred dung farmer.
I've been ducking small arms fire most of my life.
So if you can rip yourself away from scraping off roadkill along the
interstate long enough to join the hunt,
please, bring it on.
Oh,
I will, Flanagan.
I surely will.
Call ended.
Aline, can you make the car's phone untraceable?
Certainly, Fang.
The vehicle's phone tracking has gone dead, Major.
Why aren't we tracking his personal cell?
Haven't been able to. He must have a burner or an unplugged phone.
He's smart.
Well, keep trying.
Die before you, die before you, Led.
Is that a goddamn news chopper?
I can't confirm, sir.
Norm, give me a still frame of that shot.
Bingo.
Come from power above
Tell SWAT, if that bird is impeding them, they are clear to
engage.
Sir, shouldn't we try to make contact first?
I mean, the entire country is watching.
We are about to make contact, Captain.
Tankard, where are you?
Above you.
You're flying that Gazelle?
Munches, like a madman. Hey, buddy.
Hey, pal. Hey, I don't want you guys getting mixed up in this.
A little late for that, Captain. We'll keep the birds off you for as
long as we can. Take evasive maneuvers.
That's all I've been doing.
Then I guess take more evasive maneuvers.
Got to go, brother.
I don't know what you've been told.
But this ain't no easy road. Everything that
shines ain't gold. I think I need to let you know
Aline, what's the closest city?
One moment while I look that up.
You got to know
Where the hell's the suspect? You ordered SWAT to engage.
I, but, sir-
I don't give a good goddamn if the cameras see it.
That's felony obstruction
Tyler. Population
100,223.
I
just want to thank myself. Sunshine down
on me
I think they're green lit.
Thank myself. There's a lot I could do if I stood.
But I just want to thank myself. How it works would sure
help me. At least I just got to thank
Aline, I'm going to need you to find a certain kind of establishment
there
I know what keeps my soul alive. Being happy
ain't a crime. And when the world is out to leave.
Nothing goes my way
Somebody get a visual on the suspect?
So naturally. Possess-
See myself tonight.
Going to survive.
The special forces are often described by military planners
as the tip of the spear in combat operations.
A recent VA study published in the New England Journal of Medicine
found that special operations soldiers suffer from
PTSD after combat at nearly twice the
rate.
Shows of support for Flanagan are appearing across all social
media platforms, urging police restraint in any
efforts to apprehend him. We're seeing scores of viral
posts from all over the country, from veterans to
college students.
Hi.
Good afternoon.
Y'all do paint jobs?
Yeah.
What does that cost,
typically?
Running a one-day special.
Free,
for anybody
who shed blood for this country.
Now let's get that leg taken care of. Follow me.
Munch, is that an airport?
They can't follow.
F**k!
Dude, I think we hit.
Control, Black Hawk seven. Target neutralized.
Sending ground units to Walters Airfield.
Hang on.
Whoa.
Watch out! Jesus Christ!
Hey, Tank, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm going to mention to you how much I hate jail.
We're not out of the game yet.
You got a credit card on you?
Wow.
Took the liberty of changing out your plates.
Clean Texas tags.
Sure as hell ain't going to hide this dragon for too much longer.
It'll have to do.
Buddy of mine
served in Nam.
He helped you out.
I can't thank you enough.
We might've been in different wars,
still brothers.
You travel safe now.
I'm in the saddle again.
Oh, Lord, I don't want to die in Texas.
Come on, Tank, sing it with me. Where the deer and the
antelope play.
How
in
the hell did we lose him?
It's impossible.
19-7. 19-7.
Yeah, copy that.
License and registration, ma'am.
Turn
around.
The Kentucky State Police just released the name of the victim at the
crime scene Captain Flanagan fled.
He was Todd Ferris, a 58-year-old
prominent defense attorney in Louisville, who has defended many
high-profile clients, including the ex-governor.
The Louisville Courier released a story on their website about 20 minutes
ago, citing an arrest report from 2004,
charging Todd Ferris with a multimillion-dollar
real estate fraud scheme that was later dropped.
The story goes on to say that-
I believe in miracles.
Are you okay?
Hey. Are you okay?
I've been ringing you.
Tell me everything's okay.
I'm fine.
Uh-uh. I can hear it in your voice. Don't b******t me, Ryan.
Tara,
I'm good.
Where are you?
Tyler, Texas, which is charming, by the way.
Oh my God, I was so worried.
The cameras lost you for
six hours.
Where are you?
I'm at my sister's.
Also charming, by the way.
Tell me something.
Was it self-defense?
Feels like everything I do is self-defense.
That's not an answer, baby.
I did everything I could not to hurt him.
I promise.
Then he shot me in the leg.
Oh.
But it was him or me, Tara.
I swear.
Then I'm glad it was you.
Hey,
been thinking a lot about that beach.
Beach? What beach?
The one near Cancun.
Remember?
Oh,
that beach.
Locals called it La Mangusta.
Yeah. The Mongoose.
Yeah.
Why do they call it that again?
No snakes.
As I recall, we did some epic boning on that beach.
Indeed we did.
We should go back.
You mean it?
Yeah. It's my retirement plan.
Okay.
I tell you what.
You get to the Mongoose,
and we'll take it from there.
It's always been you, and only you,
my whole life.
And you for me.
Control, we're
black mega one. We're chasing a
suspect.
Come on in. Come on through.
All right, stop right there, please. Yeah, just put it in park.
Morning, Jim.
What's happening? You all right?
Looking for that runaway vet.
He robbed Fort Knox?
College's work here.
Hmm.
Making a run down to San Antonio?
Per usual.
All right.
Have a good one, Neil.
Thanks, Roy.
Still hurting?
I'll be okay.
The guy shot me back in Kentucky, in case you were wondering.
I wasn't. I'll let the state police know I seen you
crossing into Oklahoma.
Get a couple of dozen brother vet truckers to call it in, too.
By the end of the day, them bears will be hunting you in Alaska.
Thank you, brother.
I was a POW in Nam for three and a half years
God just heard me.
Every way you can figure.
Whenever I can help out a brother vet,
I feel like I'm hurting them Gods back,
just a little.
That Shelby Ol' Huntley's just crossed into New Mexico.
I seen that Shelby near Shreveport.
Yeah, that Fang guy all over the news is walking down the strip in Vegas.
Got a call. He's headed back to Kentucky.
That's h*******t. He's getting help.
From who?
Don't matter.
They all think he's John Wayne.
What,
ditch the Shelby and hide now?
This bunny ain't the hiding type.
Where would you go if you just murdered somebody?
Where's he been headed all along?
No, he can't be-
Move everybody south.
I'm going to lock up that border tighter than my stepson's search history.
I got you now, you s*n o* a b***h.
I'm riding down the quiet
line.
Not holding on, not letting go.
But I'll see you when the time is right.
Somewhere in between.
But I'm at ease with the way it rolls.
You and me again, Helene.
I'm pleased to hear that, Fang.
We could've been something, darling, if you weren't an
appliance.
I'm unable to-
Never mind.
Keep rolling.
Get back.
Hey, where are you now? Texas, I'm guessing.
But given Munch's navigational skills, it could
easily be Wyoming. She's slow, but damn, she's
maneuverable. Bear's on you. All clear for now.
Where you headed?
The Mongoose. The bar?
Beach.
A few hundred clicks south.
So?
Craving an authentic margarita.
Care to join me, boys?
Hell yeah. Hell yeah. I was looking for a new place to
retire. Yeah, same here.
Helene, I need you to find me the three nearest crossing points into
Mexico.
Captain Flanagan is making all of us who serve feel empowered.
How so?
Well, just like the rest of us, he's fighting against a system that all too often
misjudges the veterans, and is blind to their suffering.
Thank you.
Veterans organizations from across the United States have publicly
expressed solidarity with Captain Flanagan, building to the
already massive wave of support that is currently sweeping the
nation.
Destination is 200 yards ahead.
Thank you, Helene. But we're going to need to move on to option two.
Calculating route.
Control, this is 230. I am in high speed pursuit of the suspect
traveling east on Highland, three miles west 83.
We found it, sir. East on Highland before 83.
Be advised, suspect's vehicle has now changed its colors to black and its
tags to Texas. Hotel Lima Victor
Papa 0-niner-5. I repeat, color is now
black with Texas tags.
Get air pursuit to that position and all available units.
230, for a pit maneuver, moving in now. Come on.
Control, this is 230. I've lost visual of the
suspect, now heading southbound on 83.
Back off. Clear out.
This dumb farmer's about to put you in a world of s**t.
Status on the roadblocks?
In position, sir.
Love day one on three, suspect. 35, suspect at A1.
Love that, 35. 35.
As you can see on our live feed, Captain Flanagan has changed the color of
his vehicle and is continuing to evade police.
We've received reports of elevated police presence along the southern border,
indicating that law enforcement is preparing for an attempt to flee
into Mexico.
Third
rail. Roadblock ahead.
Recalculating route.
Suspect has exited the 83 heading southwest.
They tipped him off.
Well, he's got to turn back if he still wants to cross over.
No way he pulls that off.
This is our chance to block him in against the Gulf. Bring in all units.
Option three for border crossing is 44.3
miles back to the southwest.
A U-turn is not a possibility. Call the governor's office.
Have them scramble the Air National Guard.
Sir.
Everybody on point.
CNN has learned that Texas Highway Patrol
Major Walter Pope, the man leading the effort to
apprehend Flanagan, has faced three separate
state internal investigations for excessive force, none of
which led to criminal charges. CNN has reached out to Major
Pope for comment.
Status on units.
Units converging in Altona, ETA 10 minutes.
I need to inform you, Fang, that the front left tire of the
vehicle is damaged beyond repair.
Oh, really?
Control, 217. Suspect stationary on roundabout.
Car 89 en route.
151 joining.
Clear the airspace.
Yes, sir. This is Control. Clear the airspace.
Texas law enforcement has ordered local news to clear the
airspace, so we will not be able to bring you live coverage
of what is about to unfold.
Ground units cleared to engage at will.
Step out of the vehicle with your hands up.
Driver, out of the vehicle, now!
These b******s again? Get the SWAT helo up there.
It's back in Tyler.
Well, what about Air National Guard?
Viper 1, this is Control. Report your position.
Control, this is Viper 1. I'm 10 mikes out.
Step out of the vehicle. If you do not comply, we will fire upon you.
Viper 2, 451.
Now raise your hands outside the window and slowly
open the door from the outside.
I can see clearly now the rain is
gone.
I can see all obstacles in my
way.
Gone are the dark clouds that had me
blind.
It's gonna be a bright
bright sunshiny day.
Come on!
Yeah! You got me? I got you, brother.
Finally!
I can see clearly now the rain is gone.
Goodbye, Fang.
It's gonna be a bright bright
sunshiny day.
Happy days, bro.
It's gonna be a bright
bright sunshiny day.
Yeah, buddy! Where's the National Guard jet?
It should be there by now, sir.
Good.
Take him out.
You heard me.
Do it.
Viper 1, this is Control. You are cleared to engage.
Say again, Control.
I repeat, you are cleared to engage the target.
What the hell is going on?
Control, my comms are malfunctioning.
Viper 1 returning to base.
It's time for those margaritas, boys.
God dammit!
Call in the Coast Guard.
Major Pope, the FBI has jurisdiction.
Those are international waters.
I guess this one didn't end the way you saw fit, huh, Walter?
Day after day, I'm more
confused.
Yet I look for the light through the pouring rain.
You know that's a game that I hate to
lose.
And I'm feeling the strain.
Move fast.
Kick a*s.
Oh, give me the beat boys and free my soul.
I want to get lost in your rock and roll and drift away.
Captain Ryan Flanagan has escaped capture
unscathed- ... flying over international waters with
the help of his unit members.
Oh. Give me the beat boys and free my
soul. I want to get lost in your rock and roll and
drift away.
Oh, hey, hey. Give me the beat boys
and free my soul. I want to get lost in your rock and
roll and drift away.
'Cause this is Outkast country and I'm feeling
right at home.
Yeah, I ain't never going back, never gonna
be alone.
Yeah,
yeah.
Almighty heaven on high.
Oh,
preach.
Almighty heaven on high.
Oh.
Yeah, yeah. This is Outkast country and I'm feeling
right at home.
'Cause this is Outkast country and I'm feeling
Home.